{
    "id": "ee67042a720d49bf9ea03eaa6e3ae539",
    "title": "Subject And Object Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It took …………….. twenty minutes to get dressed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a8eb264da5b45c29707cfd56d4b2799"
        },
        {
            "question": "She told ……………. an interesting story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3ad8f2c25ba3489ea1e3ed3320d18988"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think we should wait for ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5eff3413bdae4fac9a6002b25250d6bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "You pay for your drinks and I will pay for …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mine",
                "my"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "382d1275b1e64328a7da56c81b34d8a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am angry with both of ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9e12eb1151a7409db173e3b877e8bc21"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you like ……………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eedbc607ee1d440fb8bc2e2a1df79a3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are ………………. coming with us?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5d356e70be5640848909a3489fe2462b"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was very kind of ……………. to help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59e36504d47b4bfdb5fc881be95486c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did ………………. recognize ………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her, him",
                "she, him",
                "she, he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b4f2b639e809477f8e0981f2721fe0ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you speak to ………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0eda66439d7740289131f7fb170fc4e9"
        }
    ]
}